## **MD. RAFIUR RAHMAN**

### **GAME DEVELOPER**



- Male
- **21/02/2001**
- **+8801731092923**
- rxrmachine@gmail.com
- https://xviirxr.github.io
- **♀** 25/1, Dhakkinkhan, Dhaka-1230

### SKILLS

### Language

Bangla, English, Hindi

### Computer

Unity3D, Photoshop, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Blender, Unreal

### **INTERESTS**

I like music, gaming and riding two wheelers.

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Hello I am Rafi. An university student and a self taught game developer working on unity for almost 4 years now. Developing new systems and tackling errors has become my passion and hobby after regular studies. After playing a vast amount of game and lack of my favorite genre I decided to build my own game, that how it started. I prefer unity as my go to game engine but I also have knowledge on Unreal and Godot game engine.

### **OBJECTIVE**

Fill in your Career's Objective

+ Shorterm (in the next 2 years).

Ex: Complete a game from a reputed studio.

+ Longterm (In the next 3-5 years).

Ex: To be an Creative Director for AAA company, running at least 3 successful project campaigns for company.

### **EDUCATION**

N.H.M.S.& C.

Intermediate

MARCH 2018 - MARCH 2020

- A College from the center of Uttara, Dhaka.

### United International University

Bachelor's degree

FEBRUARY 2021 - CURRENT

- Attending regular classes alongside game development.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

U-Topia Metaverse

Lead programmer

SEPTEMBER 2020 - MARCH 2022

U-Topia is an evolving metaverse that is seeking to build the first ethical metaverse with DAO-based governance and a Play-to-earn model.

#### Grandfleet Studios

Founder

JULY 2017 - CURRENT

A Game Dev Studio from Bangladesh. Supporting solo indie game dev's.